oddsmaker.com 2009-12-16

# Oddsmaker � Online Casino & Poker Games Privacy Policy

OddsMaker.com (The Company) is committed to protecting your privacy. The Company uses the information collected about you to track your gaming system account and game play and to provide a more personalized game playing experience. Please read on for more details about the OddsMaker.com privacy policy.

By signing up and participating in play for fun and play for free games, OddsMaker.com needs to collect your email address and mobile phone number. By signing up and participating in play for fun and play for free games you are giving The Company permission to send you announcements and special offers. If you do not wish to receive these special announcements  and offers, email [ marketing@oddsmaker.com](https://bb-exchange.q2wireless.com/owa/redir.aspx?C=ac6cc0645bbb4652980d9de8c3fb01c0&URL=mailto%3amarketing%40oddsmaker.com) with the subject heading �remove�. 

When you participate in our for real money games, The Company needs your real name, email address, and mailing address. This allows The Company to allow you access to the games you wish to participate in and to reward prizes that you win or money that you withdraw from your OddsMaker.com account.

When you submit a bug, suggestion, complaint, question, request, or any other email correspondence, The Company asks for your email address so that you can receive a response.

If you win a prize or other promotional feature, The Company may ask for your real name, mailing address, and e-mail address so that you can be notified and arrange for delivery.

By registering for an account, you agree that OddsMaker.com may display your user name and game play records. From time to time, (and usually when you win a prize), The Company may ask you to voluntarily provide general demographic and other personal information for inclusion on the OddsMaker.com "Winners" page.

In addition, The Company also reserves the right to use the information collected to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new services, and special offers you'll find valuable.

When you play games or access your account information, OddsMaker.com offers the use of a secure server. The secure socket layer (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to OddsMaker.com or sent to you. Furthermore, all of the customer data collected is protected against unauthorized access through the most up-to-date industry-standard security measures.

OddsMaker.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. The Company may release account information when The Company believes, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of OddsMaker.com, OddsMaker.com players, or others.

By using the Gaming System, you consent to the collection and use of this information by OddsMaker.com. If the OddsMaker.com privacy policy changes, those changes will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information is collected, how the information is used, and under what circumstances the information is disclosed.

Return to Top | Close this window
